At what age did you lose your virginity?
Virginity?
What is virginity?
Seriously, what is virginity?
At what age did you lose...
…did you have sex for the first time?
The first girl I ever had…
was the one who ate the whole pot of fish stew.
Then I had another one, but I lost her after throwing away her gift.
And I won’t say more because the one I was about to rape her, I lost her too.
And the one I brought to my house,
the one who ate the whole pot of fish stew,
she didn’t want me to touch her or anything.
But she ate it all, the sneaky little mole.
And I saw her breasts because she fell—she had a bruise, a big hematoma.
And her aunt also ate my fish stew at my house.
And why didn’t you get married?
I don’t wanna get married. I’m good.
Now that they see me on TV, all the girls stop me in the street.
I’m single, I’m a lone wolf.
Because if I marry one, she wins and keeps everything.
And because they watch soap operas, they come running after me.
There are soap operas for the morning, noon, afternoon, and even at night.
And when they get moody, they leave.
Do you think men and women are equal?
No, men are one thing, women are another.
I admire the way you explain things so clearly.
I said it loud and clear, didn’t I?
It’s glorious!
Did you hear they say there are gay cops now?
Yeah, I saw it in a magazine. Now you can hook up with them.
Are you thinking of coming out of the closet?
The closet? What closet?
Closet?
I put on my clothes, go out into the street, like always.
You know, when people publicly come out as gay, they “come out of the closet.”
Come out of the closet? What’s that?
Gay?
Homosexuals.
Ah, all that stuff.
Well, I don’t know anything about that.
Would you like to be a woman?
Not anymore, I’ll stay as I am.
But if I had been born a woman…
Would you have liked it?
Yeah, I’d like to be a woman. But I can’t change that.
Why would you have wanted to be born a woman?
Because women take everything, they win everything!
The ones who want to be women, even though they’re men…
Huh?
Pluma, right?
Me too.
What did you say? Pluma?
I didn’t hear what you said.
Ah, he’s gay, right?
He’s gay, right?
Do you know how to iron clothes?
A little.
Pluma.
Pluma?
Ironing clothes.
Ironing clothes, pants, yeah.
Do you know how to sew?
Yeah, a little.
Pluma.
Do you know how to scrub floors?
Damn, now you’re making me doubt myself.
He’s driving me crazy.
Just a little, just a little.
That’s what you’d be if you were the big brother.
Risitas, please,
can you tell me how many days you’ve worked
in your entire life?
How old are you?
45 years old. I don’t take age like a flower or anything.
45 years and still looking good.
Can you tell me, please, how many days you’ve worked?
I burned the papers.
The ones they gave me when I worked.
But how many days in total, more or less?
More or less…
In 45 years, have you worked at least one full year?
Seven years.
Seven. Not more than that.
Up until today.
In 45 years, seven years?
Seven.
Including vacations.
The first thing I asked when I got a job was for vacation days.
And they’d say, "Damn, you just got here, and you’re already asking for vacation!"
Really?
And what’s the hardest job you’ve ever had?
The hardest one, the hardest one… at the beach.
Working at the beach.
From morning till night.
Collecting sand?
Not sand.
I was working like crazy.
And what happened to me… I didn’t tell you?
At the…
At the kitchen.
What the cook made me do.
Clean lettuce, do the laundry, clean the fish…
And what happened with the cook that fired me.
What happened?
I didn’t tell you?
I don’t remember.
When I was in Chipiona.
I was the new guy, and the cook asks me, "You the new kitchen assistant?"
Yeah.
"Risitas, right? They told me to call you that."
The new guy. How long are you staying?
Well, today’s May, Pepe told me till September.
And what do you know how to do in the kitchen?
Clean fish, make rice…
"Alright, you’ll be the assistant here."
But for your first day, listen up.
We’re going to clean everything here.
Alright?
And then we’ll talk in the morning.
You know that when we open a restaurant,
everything has to be spotless.
Yes, chef.
We started cleaning at 11 in the morning…
The restaurant had been closed all winter,
we were getting it ready for summer.
By 2 a.m., I had scrubbed, wiped, fried, boiled—everything!
I did EVERYTHING.
And then, the chef hands me 20 paelleras.
You should’ve seen them—completely covered in mold!
"Risitas," he says,
"You can’t wash these in the sink."
And by then, my back was already killing me.
From hunching over all day, scrubbing pots and pans.
It was 2 in the morning.
And he goes, "Alright, take a break now."
"You’ve cleaned the kitchen, tomorrow we open."
"Now, take these 20 paella pans"—covered in mold—
"You listening to me?"
"Take a rope,"
"tie them up, and take them to the beach."
"Leave them in the water overnight."
"The seawater will clean off all the mold."
"But make sure you remember where you leave them!"
"Wait, what?"
"The seawater, with its salt and minerals,
will naturally clean the paella pans overnight."
"The salt will do the work."
"The salt."
"The sea, the oranges..."
I mean, I get it.
So, at 2 a.m., the chef sends me out to the beach.
"They need to understand you because you’re getting paid for this."
Oh, right. Sorry.
The magical seawater treatment.
I mean, the people down there, they understand, right?
The audience.
The salt cleans them, that’s what I meant.
Not like Holy Week, no—I'm talking about oranges.
"Risitas, take the 20 paella pans,"
"Tie them up and leave them in the sea."
"But make sure you remember where you put them,"
"because tomorrow morning you’ll have to go get them."
So at 2 a.m., I go down to the beach, and the tide is low.
I do exactly as he said—I tie them up, leave them in the water.
I stick a wooden stake in the sand as a marker.
Then I go back to the restaurant—it’s now 2:30 a.m.
"Risitas, did you do it?"
"Yes, chef."
"Alright, remember, I’ll wake you up at 8 a.m."
"Go get the paella pans then."
So I go to bed.
The restaurant is ready to open, the rice is prepped.
At 2 p.m., the chef wakes me up.
"Risitas!"
"What?"
"Go get the paella pans!"
"Let’s go, it’s already 2 p.m.!"
I throw on my swimsuit,
grab my flip-flops, half-dressed—no time to waste.
I get to the beach…
And the tide had COME BACK IN!!!
JESÚS.
I start digging around in the water, and…
I only found ONE paella pan!
Just one!
The only reason I found it was because it got stuck
between the rocks by the Chipiona lighthouse.
And when I walk back into the restaurant,
I go up to the chef… holding one single paella pan.
And he just looks at me and says—
"Where are the rest of them?"
Bend down.
Bend down and look where the water reached!
The water had reached all the way to the restaurant!
JESÚS.
"What do we do now?!"
We had two huge sacks of rice ready for the grand opening!
"CALL SEVILLE! CALL SEVILLE!"
"Tell them to bring more paella pans!!!"
JESÚS.
And there I was, standing there…
…in my swim trunks…
…holding one tiny paella pan.
And the chef just stared at me.
"Don’t just stand there! Go to Seville!"
And on the last day, when the Virgin of Regla procession passed by,
we were all in tears.
He paid me for that one little paella pan.
He gave me 500 pesetas for it.
And I never went back.
I left.
I took off walking toward Amarillo.
JESÚS.
He sent me…
He sent me—
He sent me at night!
The tide was low when I left them there… but by morning, it had come back in!
Who knows where those paella pans ended up!
They probably drifted all the way to—
—the oil tanker!
The Prestige!
Yeah, the Prestige!
And I never worked in a kitchen again.
I HATE KITCHENS!
But hey, at least he gave me a little money from the tip jar.
How much was in the tip jar?
The money he threw at me,
the money I actually earned…
…he made me pay for the 20 paella pans!
At 500 pesetas each!
I mean, you should’ve seen how I left for Seville!
I was already bored without the beach.
Oh man, we laughed so much!
Jesús, it’s fine.
I don’t want any more rice, Jesús!
Not even Chinese rice!